There is no defense.
The Juror is a thriller, crime, drama film directed by Brian Gibson.
With his gangster boss on trial for murder, a mob thug known as "the Teacher" tells Annie Laird she must talk her
fellow jurors into a not-guilty verdict, implying that he'll kill her son Oliver if she fails.
She manages to do this, but, when it becomes clear that the mobsters might want to silence her for good, she sends
Oliver abroad and tries to gather evidence of the plot against her, setting up a final showdown.
Annie Laird, played by Demi Moore.
Teacher, played by Alec Baldwin.
Oliver Laird, played by Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Juliet, played by Anne Heche.
Eddie, played by James Gandolfini.
Tallow, played by Lindsay Crouse.
The Juror is a 1996 American legal thriller film based
on the 1995 novel by George Dawes Green.
It was directed by Brian Gibson and stars Demi Moore as a single mother picked for jury
duty for a mafia trial and Alec Baldwin as a mobster sent to intimidate her.
The film received highly negative reviews and Moore won a joint Golden Raspberry Award
for Worst Actress for both her performance in this film and in Striptease.
The film explores themes of court case, jurors, blackmail, son, trial.
The tone is emotional and intense.